The morning chimes have sounded, and it's us, CJB Planning!
King Nakayama
In this project, I'm going to give you a quiz about Riko Nakayama.
I will ask you all to answer the questions.
Who knows the most about Riko Nakayama among the members?
Who knows the most about Riko Nakayama?
Ah...
Wouldn't that give us an advantage?
Yes, I'm the one.
I'm the one.
The King of the Middle Mountains.
I'm here for the three who raised their hands.
Oh, is that right?
What? What? Didn't you?
What?
I did. I asked you, why did you wear that? Why did you wear that?
Thank you, Milleries.
It was a gift. I picked it out today. I didn't buy it.
You see this combination, don't you?
I wear this a lot, and it's so easy to wear.
I'm sorry I did it twice.
Am I apologizing?
What do you think? What about you, Hoshino-san?
Did you do Rico, too?
Did you do Rico?
You seem pretty sure.
I don't remember doing it. I think I did it in a dream.
But you did it.
I'm glad it came true.
I'm going to keep aiming for it.
Yuna, are you the King of the Middle Mountains?
I don't know if that's so.
I don't know Riko best for me.
I'll put it in my name.
Nakamura Nakayama
NakamuraNakayama, you're forcing it
NakamuraYes, you all have enough enthusiasm
NakamuraYes, I think my enthusiasm is wrong NakamuraNow that I've had enough
NakamuraI understand that you are all motivated NakamuraAre you sure?
NakamuraLet's get started NakamuraReally? NakamuraReally?
NakamuraLet's begin with the first question
Question 1
NakamuraIt's a little bit dark Nakamura, only your hair is dark
NakamuraAh, so that's why
When is summer?
NakamuraSummer
What color clothes do you have the most?
Eh, but it's easy
You know? I know this one.
But you go to Lytton's exhibitions, don't you?
It's easy. This is easy.
Even I can answer that.
I can answer it myself.
I'd really like to see Nakayama for Yuna.
I'll do my best.
You can do it.
Let's start with you.
Ready, black?
Black.
Yuna.
Let's see the correct answer on the VTR.
No?
Lately it's been black.
Yay!
That's what I'm talking about.
You're very interested in me, aren't you?
Yes, I am.
It goes pretty fast.
It's easy, isn't it?
Easy, easy.
Well, it's only the first question.
Can I go now?
Second question, please.
Please tell us how you feel today in one sentence.
One Kanji sentence.
How I feel today.
What? I don't know.
I think it's pretty easy.
When was this taken, by the way?
This one.
Last year.
Six months ago.
This is where we took it together.
I'm pretty desperate for a clue, so...
He's talking now.
He's a little quiet, isn't he?
Yeah, a little quiet.
But I don't know if I can write this right now.
No way.
I don't know.
It looks like something I could write.
Well, then, maybe this is a little different.
Different?
It's like, this is what I'm supposed to write.
What?
Yeah, it's different, but...
Trust yourself.
It fits.
Oh, no, you don't.
First, Mr. Hoshino.
I'll go first.
Yes, sir.
Beautiful? Beautiful.
I wrote "tired" on the day of fatigue, but Ritto couldn't spell it.
But Ritto couldn't spell it, so I cancelled it and wrote "beautiful" because it sounded more ladylike.
It's like a compliment. I complimented her.
Next, Kobayashi-san.
Haya, haya?
It was about six months ago, in September.
It was hot. I wanted to wear fall clothes as soon as possible.
I wanted to wear fall clothes as soon as possible.
So I decided to make it early.
Then, let's continue with Yuna.
Yes, I see.
She seemed a little sleepy.
Maybe a little.
You're right, you're right, you're right, but...
Can I just answer that?
Yes, you can.
But I think you'll be impressed.
Really?
You're saying that a little differently than Tyan. It's definitely not the same thing.
Of course it is.
What is your mood today?
"Nuh-uh.
Not today's mood.
I can't feel anything.
What's that? It's always the same!
Nuh-uh.
It's always the same.
You're right.
It's always the same!
Nuh-uh is bad.
I shouldn't have thought about it.
You just thought about it.
It was stupid.
Don't think about this mountain so much.
Feel it.
I was in the cheap book.
He said the same thing.
He said I shouldn't think about it.
Feel it?
Question 3.
Now the third question.
What's your favorite country or region to visit?
Phone call.
There you go.
I'm talking.
You can do whatever you want with this.
I've been saying that since I was a little kid.
This. Isn't the quiz in the first volume easy?
You think it's easy?
No, it's fine. I really took it seriously.
Yes, sir.
Yes, for a second.
Ms. Hoshino, come in.
Canada.
Me too
Then... Oh, sorry.
Kobayashi-san, come in.
Canada
Oh!
You've already hit the jackpot.
Yuna-san.
Canada
Oh!
Correct. Correct.
Correct.
Canada.
This one too, sir.
I want all of them.
Where's the star?
Scandinavia.
Heh.
When I say I want to go to Scandinavia, they say, "Where do you want to go? I say, "Where do you want to go?
Where do you want to go? What's there?
It's the worst!
I'm coming to Scandinavia!
Uh... Swedish!
Girl Boy.
I don't know, I just... I really want to see...
I sent you after you.
That's what Sivillittan said.
Sibilittan didn't know about Sweden.
He didn't know.
He only mentioned Canada.
Yes, he only knew about Canada.
Canada!
I want to be an adult in Canada!
Not to be an adult
I want to be an adult!
But Yuna is doing this too, Konad.
I saw Riko in the past.
She was saying "Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada Canada
You were saying that, weren't you?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Can you please not betray me?
I'm sorry.
At the time, I wanted to go north.
Now...
I said it would be free, but...
It was a lost cause.
It wasn't until six months later that I realized I'd lost my mind.
It's hard to say "nothing" and stray.
It's hard.
Now the fourth question.
Question four.
If you could go back to age 0 with your current memories, what would you do?
My current memory
Difficult
If you could go back
Memory of now
My current memory, formal or otherwise.
How much of it is still there? Maybe not at all.
This is a tough one.
It feels a little bit big.
It's a little bit thumped.
I'll think about it.
It's difficult, isn't it?
I'm pretty sure I'm going to get 10 or more right.
I only got one right.
You got one right today.
I'd like to start with you, Mr. Hoshida.
Dancer
I'm going to be a dancer.
Zero years old.
0 years old dancer
0 year old dancer,
And she's a dancer, she's a dancer, she's a dancer, she's a dancer, she's a dancer, she's a dancer...
Oh, yeah, but I know what Tik-Tok is. I know what Tik-Tok is.
I can dance, so I'm going to do it.
It's going to be a hit. It's going to be a hit.
Tell me later, Mr. Kobayashi
I'm going to go into the media as a baby genius and do an MC show.
Hi. - Hi.
I can even speak the language!
I'm going to talk and say I'm going to show up Baby Genius and I'm going to get the MC show.
I'm sorry.
I'll be the MC.
Next is Yuna.
She speaks at the age of zero.
I thought they were similar.
I thought so.
That's right.
She knows all the words and phrases.
Okay, then.
Answer the question!
If you could go back to age 0 with the memories you have now, what would you do?
My current memory
Say a very difficult word at zero.
What was that?
At zero, I suddenly say more than mommy and daddy.
Can I have some milk now?
Yes, please.
Yabba baby.
I want to have a bad baby.
Oh, this is bad.
What is that? Is that weird?
Yunasan.
Point.
Yay!
Pawn, that was close.
That was close.
I knew I was being too specific.
Too specific.
You went above and beyond.
We're up. We're up.
Two points for Yuna.
That's great.
How do you feel now?
Well, I'm kind of happy for the one who thinks I don't know the most out of the three of you.
I shouldn't even think about it.
No, you shouldn't.
Next, Daiko, please share your thoughts.
What do you want to eat now?
I don't know.
This too.
If you knew me...
You should think about it.
Be me.
It's a different story if it's too salty or too sweet.
You can say this.
I think I've already answered your question. It's sweet.
Okay, okay.
You've got two choices.
It's two more choices.
It's sweet.
I don't know.
The sweet one.
I'm so confused.
I want to eat the sweet one.
I want the sweet one.
How old are you, zero?
I want something sweet!
I'll eat it in front of Yuna.
Sure.
It might be totally right.
I might have eaten it. I have no idea.
Maybe it's salty.
If it was salty, what would it be?
One dish at a time.
I want to eat it.
It's sweet.
There are two choices for sweet.
I was wondering which one it was,
When I said I've never eaten in front of Yuna,
It's this one.
I feel like they're probably the same.
I'm confused.
I'll go with what I know.
Oh!
This way, then.
Here you go.
Here we go.
Fresh cream.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Next, Kobayashi-san.
Yes, sir.
Fresh cream.
I knew it.
Oh!
Then, Yuna-san.
Grumboo.
I knew it.
That's great.
Yuna is like a Liquipedia.
Sure, we've only known each other for a year or two.
But I do read wikipedia.
I see.
So you're a wikipedia reader.
Prolificer.
No, I don't like it.
Like pedia.
Rittan likes whipped cream so much that I often see him eat only whipped cream,
Usually if it's a cake or something, you want to eat strawberries or something.
But Riko is different. She only takes the whipped cream.
By the way, the whipped cream and the other one is cream puffs.
I like cream puffs, so it's one or the other.
I was torn between chocolate and cream puffs.
I understand.
You understand?
I get it. I get it.
I get it.
I see.
When Rittan bugs me, he eats a lot of chocolate.
I was eating a little.
Now, let's see the correct answer.
What do you want to eat now?
Mmm...
Whipped cream.
Yay!
Cream puffs.
You said cream puffs, right?
What? What the hell?
What is it?
Fresh cream and custard cream puffs.
What the hell?
It's so difficult!
By the way, I said the other one was cream puffs.
I did, but I didn't write it down.
That's okay.
Why did I say it?
Then I have to say whipped cream.
Okay, then. Question 6.
Go ahead.
What's your favorite prefecture?
Wait, that's too hard!
It's so hard!
It was hard for me too.
Oh, no, it's hard!
I had a hard time with the hints too.
But you know, I've been to a lot of places, and you've given me a lot of opportunities.
That's why I came up with this answer.
There were three.
Hokkaido, Okinawa, Nagasaki.
Nagasaki... oh!
I was thinking Hokkaido, too.
Fukuoka by hope.
I know, right?
But you love it.
Yes, and I love it there.
What?
Wait, I don't know.
Have you been there?
I have been there.
Have you ever been there for anything other than what you want?
I have.
You've been so good to me.
You've been very good to me.
You've been a big help to me in so many ways.
I'm sure.
Well then...
Hoshida-san, go ahead.
Hokkaido.
You went there with Ayaka, right?
That's why you went on a private trip.
I didn't go without my parents.
I don't remember that.
So I guess it was fun.
Next is Ms. Kobayashi.
Not just in one prefecture, but all over the country.
All over the country.
Next, Mr. Yuto
I hope to go to a new city called Fukuoka.
Will it live up to your expectations?
I don't know.
Okay, here's your answer.
What's your favorite prefecture?
Uh-huh?
Favorite prefecture?
I was born in Tokyo, so let's go to Tokyo.
Oh, wow.
You see, I'm telling you.
What's that?
That's a tough one.
Prefectures are difficult.
That's exactly what Yuna says.
Fukuoka, Hiroshima, I want all the families in Japan to go to their own prefectures.
Tokyo... but... people from Tokyo don't say much about it.
They say they were born and raised in Tokyo.
That's a rare type of person.
That's true.
I love Tokyo, too.
We've thought about it.
We're all over the place, aren't we?
We'll think about it... and the next one, too.
We'll definitely think about it.
Don't think about anything. Just write it down.
Next, Question 7, please.
Question 7.
What is your favorite animal?
Favorite animal
Favorite animal.
I think you're easily offended.
I can tell.
At times like this...
I might get angry.
What? Oh, my God.
Isn't this it?
Is this okay? That's it.
It's okay.
Is it too soon?
It's the only way.
Maybe we should think about it.
No, I think I'm done.
Okay, Hoshida-san.
Ugh! It's not a dog anymore.
No!
Okay, Kobayashi...
A dog.
I think it is.
Everyone!
Oh!
You're all the same.
They don't call it a dog.
I'll take that as a no-no.
Okay, here's your answer.
What is your favorite animal?
My favorite animal is a dog.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay, okay. I'm a dog.
What?
What the fuck?
What? What?
I'm sorry. It's Seira.
Thank you very much.
What? Really.
It's a dog.
Can I have a dog?
Boo-boo. In and out.
There's something else.
Yes, yes, yes, now give me the answer
Now you've got to be right on point!
A slider at the very last minute, a 7-Eleven whipped cream...
I'm sure it's more in line with what I'm saying than what I'm saying it's the right answer.
Yeah, it's true.
It's different, isn't it?
It's just that sometimes I forget the first time.
Let's go to the last one.
The eighth question, please.
The last one.
What's the first thing you remember in your life?
This is a difficult one.
My earliest memory in life...
It was at a gathering.
At a gathering at a human site.
On the way home
Oh, my God.
Grandpa got drunk.
He was...
He was, what, five years old?
No, I think I was five?
I remember being about five or six.
What's your first experience in life? What is the first experience in your life?
I have a lot of firsts.
What?
Do you remember being born?
What? Even now?
I thought I did because I talked, but I remembered before that.
I remember when I talked, but I don't remember now.
I remembered when I was in elementary school.
Oh, wow.
Do you remember it now?
I wonder.
I was in high school at a family reunion,
My grandma saw my head then.
She said I had a split skull.
I don't remember that, it was kind of sad.
I had a gut split, something like that, when I was really tiny.
I had a split here.
Oh, yeah.
Like I wanted to see it right in front of me.
Yeah, one word.
That was your first word?
A word.
One word.
I'm glad you're better.
Good, good, good.
You look beautiful.
I'm 55.
Fifty-five. Fifty-five in my house is rare.
Okay, Mirei, you're up first.
Come on in, Mirei.
Hey...
At New Year's, a drunken old man took me around on his shoulders
Oh!
Isn't that like a relative?
We get together like relatives.
I don't get it.
Next is Mr. Kobayashi.
The simple moment when grandpa fell down.
He got drunk and fell down.
I got drunk and fell down.
But I didn't tell you this...
But I didn't tell you this... Grandpa reverse-engineered it with his name.
I heard that's true.
Riko seems to laugh and talk about this kind of thing.
Of course.
You've lived quite a long time, but you still don't know what your own drink tastes like.
That's true.
That's worrisome.
That's worrisome, isn't it?
That's for sure.
I'll tell you what I'm worried about.
What's the first thing you remember in your life?
Yesterday.
I wonder.
I don't know.
I was about five years old.
A relative.
on a boat.
Nice chicken.
Was it a good chicken?
To the wind.
With the wind.
Instead, Grandpa got really drunk.
He fell down the escalator.
But he was unharmed.
He was strong.
I still remember thinking how strong he was.
Rolling down the escalator.
Not strong?
What's this?
What about this one?
What about this?
Did you fall?
I said I fell.
Are you sure it's in?
Yes, I'm sure.
So, Mr. Kobayashi, here we go.
Yay!
This episode is amazing!
Grandpa was so creepy!
Grandpa's shoulders, and Grandma's under his shoulders.
Grandma was fine.
But she just got up and was fine.
I thought, "This guy is the strongest.
You don't feel the pain so much, Riko.
That's a genetic trait.
You inherited it from your grandfather.
Heredity.
So, all problems are over!
Awesome.
I looked at the points
Hoshino-san has 1 point
Mr. Kobayashi has 3 points
Nakamura-san has 2 points
So it is the 1st Nakayama over Kobayashi-san!
Thank you for your hard work
That's what I'm talking about!
Thank you very much.
Mr. Kobayashi, the winner, what would you like to say?
Your name.
Actually, I secretly have a Mayamao.
We did Mayamao, just the two of us.
It was just you, me and Mayamao.
I wonder if it's a phantom, this time.
Why?
We didn't get Yasumoto last time.
Who got Yasumoto?
Maya got it.
It's been a long time coming.
That's why I'm so happy.
Thank you very much.
But I'm pretty sure we can all answer the question: What's your favorite animal? Huh? Huh?
You answered it.
You did.
I'm pretty sure I missed it.
It's hard.
I'm gonna get all the answers right.
I wish I could tell you... of course it's stupid, but I won't make you do it again.
I'd prefer whipped cream, but I got it.
Oh, yeah, sure.
I'll see you all in the future.
Takayama drinking, really!
Next time we'll stand up.
It's complicated.
Subscribe to our channel
Good Button
Comment
Please turn on notifications
bye-bye